<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Apps</string>
    <string name="test_view">Text View</string>
    <string name="my_openion">I am interested in my android course in online view.</string>
    <string name="large_text">Tree plantation means planting trees more and more. Trees are part and parcel of our environment. Trees are useful to us in many ways.
        They give us foods, fruits, medicines, woods, flowers, shades etc. They also give us oxygen and take in carbon dioxide.They keep the balance of the environment.
        They protect us from various kinds of natural calamities like floods, droughts, storms, cyclones etc. But people cut down trees and endanger our own lives.
        Cutting down trees causes serious damage to the soil.
        \n \n
        It also causes global warming which may bring about a serious cause of sufferings to the human beings in the near future. Trees are our best friends.
        So, we should not cut and use trees at random. Rather we should plant more trees for a healthier, happier and better life.Trees are an essential part
        of ordainment There can be no doubt about the usefulness of trees. We need oxygen for living and trees to provide us with oxygen. Trees cause rainfall
        and thus prevent the spread of desert. Trees save our land from erosion and maintain the fertility of the soil.Trees give us shade. Trees give us food. We
        get crops and different delicious and juicy fruits from trees. Trees give shelter to many animals, insects, and birds.
        In this Way, trees help maintain ecological balance. We also get many products like wood, leaves, rubber, resin, fragrance honey etc.Paper is made from Wood
        and bamboo. We use wood as fuel and also need it for making things like houses, boats, and furniture. Trees make our world beautiful. It is very charming to
        look at trees. But the world is losing its trees in huge amount every year.
        \n \n
        We cut a lot of trees and destroy many forests for frazzling $30 cities, making new houses and for getting more Wood. If this trend continues, there will not
        be enough trees for maintaining ecological balances. Many countries are already turning into deserts due to the massive cutting of trees.Many species of birds
        and animals have also become extinct for want of food and habitat after the destruction of forests. Hence it has become an emergency to plant more trees. In
        Bangladesh, the rainy season is the best time for the plantation of trees. We can plant trees in any open places.around our houses, office buildings, factories,
        schools colleges, and hospitals. We should also plant trees on either side of the roads and in all available places.
    </string>
    <string name="login_button">Login</string>
    <string name="logout_button">Logout</string>
</resources>
